[{"answer": "I think because he -- he tried.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "Why did you feel differently about your father?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "I can't believe that they gave me stick for writing a book that's the truth and I stopped before the verdict.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Should a network, NBC, or anybody else, be airing this documentary, do you think?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Is there a part of you, Jermaine or your family, curious to hear what he has to say?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "We asked NBC to comment.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "So what's going to come out of his mouth?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "What I was feeling, I felt the same, because this is just a process we're going through.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "In that moment, what did you all feel?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "I felt for my mother.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "How did you -- how did you react to that when you knew that was happening?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Never heard him like that.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Had you ever heard Michael like that?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Never, ever, ever.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Had any of the family ever heard?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "He was probably going to use it.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Well, what did you think they were?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Because he's a liar.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Why would anyone tape him like that?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Ben wasn't -- no.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Was Ben not available?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "I think we are headed for a very close, hard-fought election, and the thing is I would have said the same thing to you about how close this election would be the week that bin Laden was killed and we're creating 200,000 jobs a month as I would say now when we're having a little bit tougher of an economic situation.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Where do you think things are from the White House point of view as we sit?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Well, he is quite cool under pressure.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Or is he just quite cool under pressure?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's important to understand the mess this president inherited, to understand we didn't get into the mess overnight, we're not going to get out of it overnight.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "And how much do you guys have to take it on the chin now for the actions that you've taken?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "No --", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Is it helpful to have a former Democrat president who's so popular out there giving his version of how to get America back to work, or would you rather he just kept it quiet a bit?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Well, he does it privately and publicly, and it's helpful in both cases.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Do it privately to the president?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, they say the economy is all -- the better the economy is, the better it is for the incumbent president.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "And conversely, if they go up from where we are now, if they go much higher than, say, 9.5 percent or something, that you'd be in real trouble?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Well, I think it speaks to real uncertainty on their side about who the right candidate is.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What do you make of their battle so far?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "I'm not an expert on Republican primary politics.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "And what do you think of the prospect potentially of a black American against a black American in an American presidential race, which has never happened before?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Well, I think, you know, he's always appreciated Mitt Romney's -- Governor Romney's leadership in passing his health care bill in Massachusetts.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "What does the president think of Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- you know, this president came to Washington wanting to change politics here and change the political tone and bring people together.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Where do you think you have been least successful?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Yes, someone jokingly said to us the other day that our bumper sticker should be: \"Bin Laden's dead, G.M.'s alive,\" which I think that would be a great bumper sticker and maybe the campaign would sell t-shirts to that effect.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "What are the kind of words you would like to see as a cornerstone of the next campaign which have perhaps a better chance of overall success?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "That's a part of it, but it's more than just the Americans who aren't working.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "But will it come down to basically -- \"I will get America back to work\" as an election pledge, a look in his eyes and either believe him or believe his opponent?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Did you feel that when you finished it, that you -- when you closed the book and thought, that's my life?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Because I just thought of you as this funny guy who does Donald Trump and Bill Clinton on \"Saturday Night Live.\"", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Well, it's -- that's a lot -- that's a lot of -- that's a lot to think about.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "What -- what's that done to your life?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "And it went on.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "I spent most of my life, I guess, recovering from moments like that, you know?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Do you have any theories yourself about why your mother --", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "It does happen, you know?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I think she was abused.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "She'd been abused?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I called her and said I'm -- I'm in therapy for trauma and child abuse and -- and worse.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "As you got older, what was your relationship with your mother like?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I was already on \"Saturday Night Live.\"", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "What age were you then?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Not until her death bed.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Did you have any more contact with her?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "I felt nothing.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "And how did that make you feel, when she died?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Well, it's not surprising to me that you're so emotional about this.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "I was very moved by my father, you know?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I think because he -- he tried.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Why did you feel differently about your father?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Yes, sure.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Can I have a nap -- a tissue or something?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Was he aware of what your mother was doing?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "For not -- for not being there as good as he wanted to be.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "He was apologetic for his own negligence toward you?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I guess Clinton is the one that -- that you get the most mileage out of.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Which was your favorite?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Where?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "No, just right before it.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "-- colonoscopy?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Once in a while.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "So you -- you do it, you say?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "My favorite was Donald Trump.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "I think we should play you something now, got a tribute to you --", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Well, he's been amazing.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "What do you make of his impression?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "I guess from my mom.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Where go you get the ability to do impressions from, do you think?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Really good.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Coaches, teachers, people in the neighborhood.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Who would she do?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "She was -- yes, pretty incredible and --", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Anyone -- anyone that she picked up?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "And would make you laugh?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "It just would change her.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Have you been able to forgive her in your mind?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "Well, I was going to ask you, were you ever high when you were on the air?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "You were never tempted?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Are you clean now?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "Well, I haven't done as well as I wanted to with that.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "You don't drink or take drugs at all?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "AMMOND: I think so.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Are you happier than you've been before?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Do you think your \"Saturday Night Live\" costars will be shocked by this book?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Did they know about your mother and stuff?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "It was pretty damned bad.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "How bad was the incident?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "Actually from -- I think that on the book it says the offices, I was taken to the office -- this actually was a clinic underneath the theater, yes.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "From the studio?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "It did.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "ORGAN: How could this have been going on with this guy, who just seems like he's the happiest, funniest guy you'd ever meet?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "Well, I'm doing \"Are We There Yet?\"", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "What are you doing, career-wise, now?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "I just want to play Truman Capote on Broadway.", "docId": "111109pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "What ambitions do you have professionally and personally?", "qSentId": 741}]